Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jserranocrenyc (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Lead Generation
Customer Success
CRM Software

Languages

Spanish (Native or Bilingual) English (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Florida Real Estate License

Jorge Serrano

Construction Tech | SaaS | Real Estate

Brooklyn, New York, United States

Summary

I am an experienced professional excelling in customer service and sales. Fluent in English and Spanish, with a strong capacity for effective cross-cultural communication. Demonstrated success in leading international sales teams and managing complex customer relations, especially in collections. Technologically adept with Salesforce and Salesloft. Background as a professional athlete with the Philadelphia Phillies, showcasing discipline, teamwork, and resilience. A versatile and committed individual, offering a unique blend of skills to drive growth and enhance customer experiences in various industries.

Experience

Beti BDR

February 2024 - Present (3 months)

Brooklyn, New York, United States

homerich realty

2 years 7 months

Sales Development Representative

April 2022 - February 2024 (1 year 11 months)

Miami-Fort Lauderdale Area | Remote

- Coordinated efforts with Broker to optimize international sales strategy for the company
- Provide end to end direction for foreign nationals looking to invest in Soflo real estate market
- Source, develop and close on international leads

Real Estate Consultant

August 2021 - May 2023 (1 year 10 months)

Weston, Florida, United States

American Express

Collections Agent

May 2020 - May 2021 (1 year 1 month)

Fort Lauderdale, Florida, United States

- Responsible for loans and customer credit assessments for accounts over \$25k in balances
- Negotiated increases with customers on their existing LOC

Philadelphia Phillies
Professional Baseball Player
May 2011 - August 2015 (4 years 4 months)

Clearwater, Florida, United States

Education

Arizona State University
Bachelor of Science - BS, Political Science

Activity

04/18/2024, Imeila Fonua added candidate to BDR- Test Sample